

# **Mohit Vijeta**

+61-403440071 mohitvijeta698@gmail.c

om

2/77 clow street,Dandenong, 3175, VIC

in https://www.linkedin.co m/in/mohit-vijeta/

### Skills

#### **Technical Skills**

- HTML5, CSS3
- React, JavaScript ES6
- MySQL, RHEL 9, GitHub
- Python, Java
- Django Web Framework

#### **Soft Skills**

- Logical Thinking & Problem Solving
- Team Collaboration & Leadership

### **Project**

- Data Analysis for 20-Minute Neighborhood Application. Conducted Primary Research on IoT Technology for the City of Casey. Role- Project Leader and Business Analyst (February 22- November 2022)
- Web Design of organization website
  VicWise <a href="https://vicwise.org/">https://vicwise.org/</a> Role-Front-end Developer
- Personal Portfolio Website with the help of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React.
- React base Calculator with the react library Reference
- Sunil Rane- sunilsrane@gmail.com Head of Information Security & Cloud Infrastructure (CISO)
- Sumeet Nagpalsnagpal@casey.vic.gov.au
   City of Casey Project Manager

### **Summary**

A rigorous, task-driven professional with substantial experience in Web Development, E-commerce, FB, IG and TikTok Ads, and Project Management. Adept at using strong interpersonal and communication skills to interact with diverse individuals and groups at all Enterprise levels.

An Enthusiastic undergraduate with a qualification in Information Technology. Possess excellent analytical and critical thinking abilities, hoping to increase product customer satisfaction while achieving corporate objectives.

# **Work Experience**

### May 2022- Current

Volunteering with Vic Wise in a Web development team with a front-end developer position. Focused on brand awareness, and user experience. The application used are – WIX and WordPress websites.

#### • June 2021- Oct 2022

Entrepreneur in e-commerce store with the Dropshipping business. Store built with Shopify application and used the agile approach with store development. The startup was **BellySecure™**, **PetSmilesCo™** with the existence of IG and FB pages.

### • Sep 2022- Oct 2022

Student Consultant Placement with Global Victoria Intellect. Mini Hippo Pty Ltd.(mysqueeze.com.au). Conducted thorough market research to attract potential customers and upscale the business.

# **Education**

### • April 2023- July 2023

Earned Professional Certificates from Meta in Specializations of Introduction Front-end Development, JavaScript, Version Control, HTML and CSS in depth, Basic and Advance React, and Front-End Developer Capstone.

### • July 2019- April 2023

Completed Bachelor's of Information Technology Degree (General).

#### • July 2022- Feb 2023

Completed Red Hat Certified System Administrator RH124 and RH134.

#### • April 2023- Current

Learning AWS Associate Solution Architecture Certification.